It begins with an ancient warning. It ends at the edge of Niagara Falls. In
between there are 5 murders. Solve the mystery. Or die trying.
Last Embrace is a thriller, mystery, romance film directed by Jonathan Demme.
Secret agent Harry Hannan suffers a mental breakdown when a botched
mission in Mexico results in the death of his wife.
He is sent to a mental asylum, after which he eventually returns to work.
But, once again, he begins to doubt his sanity when he
receives a bizarre death threat written in Hebrew.
Not knowing which of his colleagues wants to kill him, Hannan teams up with pretty
young college student Ellie Fabian to attempt to unravel the mystery.
Harry Hannan, played by Roy Scheider.
Ellie Fabian, played by Janet Margolin.
Richard Peabody, played by John Glover.
Sam Urdell, played by Sam Levene.
Dave Quittle, played by Charles Napier.
Eckart, played by Christopher Walken.
Last Embrace is a 1979 American neo-noir thriller
film directed by Jonathan Demme.
Very loosely based on the novel The 13th Man by Murray Teigh
Bloom, it stars Roy Scheider and Janet Margolin.
The film explores themes of obsession, spy, paranoia, suspicion, niagara falls.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.